有人吗
Hello?
放老子出去
Let me the fuck out!
你他妈是谁
Who the fuck are you?
没想到你这么矮小
You're smaller than I thought you'd be,
我觉得很奇怪
which is strange because you
你居然能把训练教官胖揍一顿
did a hell of a number on your drill instructor
他可不是吃素的
and he's not a pussy.
这应该不是你第一次
Probably not the first
因为暴脾气而惹上麻烦吧
time your temper got you into trouble, is it?
可能你就是
That's probably why you
因此才参军的  对吧
joined the army in the first place, right?
还是说你参军是因为爱国
Or are you just a patriot?
这是什么地方
Where am I?
你该问这不是什么地方
Where aren't you?
这里不是本宁堡的禁闭室
You aren't in the brig at Fort Benning
也不会有军事法庭判你在军事监狱蹲两年
facing a court-martial that could have landed you two years
然后把你变成比现在还混蛋的混蛋
in military prison and turned you into an even meaner asshole than you are now.
我把你转出来了
I had you moved.
不用谢
You're welcome.
那到底是什么
So what is this?
应该是数学课吧
Well, I guess it's math class,
我没穿军装没戴徽章
because I'm not wearing a rank or an insignia
这里也不是监狱  那么
and this isn't a cell, so
特种部队吗
Special Ops?
去死
Hey, fuck you!
我去死
Fuck me?
过几天见  小子
We'll see you in a couple days, kid.
什么  你去哪里
What? Where are you going?
等等
Hey!
混蛋  给我回来
Hey, asshole, come back!
回来
Hey!
放老子出去
Let me the fuck outta here!
《黑吃黑》第三季 第十集[本季终]
Banshee S03E10
见到你很荣幸
It's an honor to meet you.
我说了  我是你的铁杆粉丝
Like I said, I'm a huge fan.
贱人  我不知道你把我当成谁
Bitch, I don't know who you think I am...
你是贾伯  传说中的贾伯
You're Job. The Job.
91年你黑进加拉加斯国家银行
In '91, you hacked Banco Nacional of Caracas
转移了七百万美金
and transferred $7 million
给南美的人道主义非营利组织
to humanitarian nonprofits across South America.
半年后  你又用僵尸病毒感染了
Six months later, you infected the mainframe of Wing-Lijun Shipping
文氏船运公司的系统  造成近一亿美元损失
with a botnet virus that cost them almost 100 million--
我知道你在用英语叨逼
I know the words coming out your face are technically English,
但我不知道你叨逼的是什么
but I still don't know what the fuck you talking about.
我在网络犯罪部花了七年时间追踪你
I spent seven years at cybercrimes tracking you,
研究你的作案手法
studying your work.
你黑进军械库这次
The hack into the armory,
与其他案子相比  真是小菜一碟
that was simple compared with your other efforts.
但是你关掉我们电网的定时逆变手法
But the way you pulled off the timed reverse on our power grid--
世界上可能只有两三个人
I mean, there are maybe two or three other hackers
有那个本事  但他们都在中国
who could have pulled that off and they live in China.
那你为什么不去中国
Then why don't you fuck off over there
把他们叨逼死呢
and bore them to death?
1994年你渗透进国安局数据库
In '94, you infiltrated the NSA database
删除了40项
and deleted the personnel
秘密军事行动的人事记录
records of 40 covert military operatives.
我猜
My theory--
其实你只需要让一个人销声匿迹
you just needed to disappear one guy.
但是你做事谨慎小心
But you were just being thorough,
一如既往
as always.
就是这件事让中情局彻底盯上了你
Well, that one put you on the CIA's radar for good.
我再跟你说一遍
I would tell you again
你认错人了
you have mistaken me for someone else
但是你好像很兴奋
but you seem so goddamn excited,
我不想扫了你的兴  利奥
I hate to ruin your fun, Leo.
你就是传说中的金奖券  贾伯
You're the golden ticket, Job.
我一定会从你身上捞到好处
And I am going to cash you in.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你鲁莽  不计后果
You're impetuous, reckless.
-你违背了我  -我以为那是在帮你
- You defied me. - I thought I was helping you.
谢谢你  博登
Thank you, Burton.
去把车开过来
Bring the car around.
早在你出生之前
I've been dealing with men
我就跟弗拉奇尔
like Frazier and Morales
莫拉莱斯这样的人打交道了
since before you were born.
你要慢慢学  瑞贝卡
You'll learn, Rebecca.
但学之前  得先明白
But in order to learn, you have to accept the fact
你并不是无所不知
that you don't know anything.
至少现在不是
Not yet.
我明白
I understand.
话说回来  我们都会犯错
Having said that, we've both made mistakes,
但是这些错误不能再犯了
mistakes that can never happen again.
你要去费城吗
Are you going to Philadelphia?
我们都要去
We all are.
你他妈放开我
Man, get the fuck off of me.
够了
Hey, that's enough!
别想碰她  混蛋
Don't even think about it, asshole.
见鬼  你还好吗  贾伯
Shit, are you okay, Job?
你他妈问的这是什么蠢问题
What the fuck kind of stupid-ass question is that?
他没事
He's okay.
你知道斯托是怎么找上我们的吗
You got any idea how Stowe landed on us?
我们大意了
We got sloppy.
但他还没查明一切
Well, he doesn't know everything,
所以我们才有命等救援
and that's the only thing keeping us alive until help arrives.
是吗  那他该找谁帮忙呢
Yeah? And who's gonna help him, hmm?
他只有三个朋友  全在这了
That man has exactly three friends and they all right here.
有点信心好吗
Have some faith, huh?
我就这样
Have you met me?
他会来的
He's gonna come.
我知道他会来
Oh, I know he'll come.
他会他妈的带着整队人来
He'll take on the whole motherfucking platoon.
没准还能通过大门
Might even make it past the front gate.
就算那样  他和我们之间
But there's still a shitload of mercs
还隔着一堆武装雇佣兵
with a shitload of guns between him and us.
我要见斯托上校
I need to see Colonel Stowe.
我们是老相识了
We're old friends.
除非你他妈给我开门  否则我不会走
I'm not leaving till you open that fucking gate.
他会有办法的
He'll find a way.
去你妈的  有屁办法
Fuck you, he'll find a way.
他可不是你的神仙教母
He ain't your fairy godmother
能实现你的所有梦想
come to make all your dreams come true.
你还要让他为你
How many more times
出生入死多少次
does he have to put his ass on the line for you
总有一天  他脑袋要他妈开花了
until he gets his motherfucking head blown off?
你是在怪我吗
You're blaming me for this?
是谁他妈把目标操了个爽
I ain't the one who fucked the mark!
-去你妈的  贾伯  -不  去你妈的  卡莉
- Oh, fuck you, Job. - No, fuck you, Carrie.
或是安娜
Or Ana.
谁他妈知道你现在叫啥名字
Or whatever the fuck you calling yourself today.
既然你这么担心
If you were so worried...
你那男朋友怎么可能知道...
How'd your boyfriend know exactly...
你完全可以叫停这次的任务
...you could have shut this job down.
-我很专业  -你他妈泄露了什么
- I'm a professional. - What the fuck did you let slip?
你说你到底告诉那个混蛋什么了
You tell me what you told that motherfucker!
你居然敢这么说
How dare you?
你俩都他妈给我闭嘴
Both of you shut the fuck up!
如果我们得死  那就死吧
If we're gonna die, then we're gonna die.
但也起码有点尊严好吗  操
Have some motherfucking dignity for fuck's sake.
贾伯
Job...
她要是泄露了什么  我们四个早就死了
if she slipped up, the four of us would be dead already.
我们要活着出去
We gonna make it out of here alive,
就必须要团结
we got to stick together.
好吗
Yeah?
请进
Come.
-你来这里干什么  -刚好路过
- What are you doing here? - I was in the neighborhood.
我没时间和你玩游戏
I don't have time for games.
你要是有事找我  就快点说
If you have business with me, get to it.
怎么了  上校  出什么事了吗
What's going on, Colonel? Everything okay?
听着  警长  我只能认为
Look, Sheriff, I can only imagine
你的生活很无聊  很卑微
how boring and insignificant your life must be,
但说实话  我根本不在乎
but honestly, I don't give two shits.
如果你没什么屁事的话
If you don't have a reason to be here,
就他妈滚出我的基地
then get the fuck off my base.
我有六百万的理由
I got six million reasons.
原来警长是贼
The sheriff is a thief.
我其实不是警长
I'm not really a sheriff.
你是来这里谈判的吗
You've come here to negotiate?
我是来告诉你  如果你不放了我的朋友
I came here to tell you that if you don't let my friends go,
就再也见不到你的钱了
you'll never see your money again.
我可以把你关在这
I can keep you here,
一个个的砍掉你的手指
remove your fingers one by one
直到你告诉我那些钱的下落
until you tell me where the cash is.
你我都清楚  来这儿之前我做好了准备
We both know I wouldn't have come here without insurance.
现在  我也不知道你的钱在哪儿
Right now I have no clue where your money is.
如果我半小时没回去的话
And if I'm not back in half an hour,
会有人打电话给刑事调查局
my insurance is gonna call CID.
你曾经当过兵
You've been a soldier.
我猜你曾经浪费了你所有的机会
My guess is you wasted every opportunity you ever had,
辜负了所有对你有期待的人
disappointed everyone who ever took a chance on you.
这是你这种不服从命令的混蛋最擅长的
It's what insubordinate assholes like you do best.
你背叛了自己的潜力
You betray your own potential.
你还挺会说教
Wow, you're really good at this.
我他妈的要我的钱
I want my fucking money!
我要保证能活着
I want proof of life.
渴吗
Thirsty?
你脱水了
You're dehydrated.
你的器官要开始停止工作了
Your organs are starting to shut down.
我肯定你能感觉到  头疼  发冷
Sure you can feel it. The headaches, the chills.
很快幻觉会变得很强烈
Soon the hallucinations will become so intense,
你会失去现实的感觉
you'll lose all sense of reality.
和我说实话  我给你回报
Tell me the truth. I will reward you.
你母亲的名字是什么
What was your mother's name?
凯瑟琳
Catherine.
凯瑟琳  是个好母亲吗
Catherine. Was she a good mother?
我想是的
I guess so.
你要更确定一点儿
I'm gonna need you to be more definitive with me.
她是个好母亲吗
Was she a good mother?
-是的  -是的
- Yes. - Yes.
-你爱她吗  -是的
- Did you love her? - Yes.
是的
Yes.
你父亲的名字是丹尼斯
Your father's name was Dennis.
丹尼斯
Dennis.
-你也爱他吗  -是的
- Did you love him, too? - Yes.
你父亲经常暴打你的母亲
Your father regularly beat the shit out of your mother.
让她进了六次医院
Put her in the hospital six times.
他也打你  不是吗
He beat you, too, didn't he?
-不是  -他当然打了
- No. - Of course he did.
-没有  -他就是打了
所以你杀了他
That's why you had to kill him.
我没有杀他
I didn't kill him.
你当然杀了他
Of course you killed him.
他是坏人  让你痛苦
He was a horrible man who made you suffer.
他让你和你母亲痛苦
He made you and your mother suffer.
你杀了他  告诉我你杀了他
And you killed him. Just tell me that you killed him.
告诉我真相  我想让你告诉我真相
Hmm? Tell me the truth. Now I want you to tell me the truth.
-我没有杀他  -我只想听实话
- I didn't kill him. - All I want you to do is tell me the truth.
-不  -我想让你跟我说
- No. - I want you to say to me,
我杀了我的父亲  我想让你承认
"I killed my father." I want you to admit it.
告诉我你杀了他
Tell me that you killed him.
你是安全的  你和我在一起  你要让他痛苦
You're safe. You're here with me. You had to make him suffer.
-我没有杀他  -快承认你杀了你的父亲
- I didn't kill him. - Just admit that you killed your father.
告诉我真相  告诉我你杀了他
Tell me the truth. Tell me that you killed him.
-我杀了他  -什么
- I killed him. - What?
-什么  -我杀了他
- What? - I killed him.
什么
What?
我杀了他
I killed him.
给你  给你
Here you go. Here you go.
喝吧
Drink, drink, drink.
你看  你的朋友们都还活着
As you can see, your friends are all alive.
暂时活着
For the moment.
去把我的钱拿回来
Go get my fucking money.
我要关照你一下
I'm gonna pay a little visit.
我们还没好好打过招呼呢  酒保
We haven't really gotten acquainted, bartender.
你好  柯特
Hello, Kurt.
-加尔文  -好久不见
- Calvin. - It's been a long time.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
还不错吧
Not bad, huh?
是的
Yeah.
你离开的那晚
You know, when you disappeared that night,
我以为你只是需要点时间冷静一下
I thought you just needed to clear your head for a minute.
但没想到这么久
But this is a lot to take in.
没错
I'm sure.
现在你又回来  和离开时一样突然
Now you're back just as suddenly as you left, huh?
是时候回家了
It was time to come home.
对
Right.
你残忍地离我们而去  柯特
You left us in the lurch that night, Kurt.
有人追杀你  找你报仇
There were some who wanted to hunt you down, make you pay.
是我护着你
But I defended you.
为了你我骗了兄弟会
I lied to the Brotherhood for you.
但你又突然回来了
And now you come back here unannounced
还对贾斯帕和布莱斯大打出手
and you do what you did to Jasper and Bryce.
现在我也很难保你周全了
You're making it very hard for me to keep you safe.
是吗
Am I?
不过...
Still...
血浓于水
you're my blood.
你总是说  再亲亲不过亲兄弟
And like you always said, brothers before Brotherhood, right?
所以  哥  我给你一个机会改正
So, big brother, I'm gonna give you a chance to do the right thing.
你脱掉这身警服
You take off this uniform
回到你真正的家族中
and you come back to your real family.
我会摆平一切
I'll smooth things over.
就像过去你保护我那样
I'll get you in the way you got me in back in the day.
我要做对的事
I am going to do the right thing.
我要把兄弟会关了
I'm gonna shut down the Brotherhood.
所有的一切
All of it.
加尔文  你好好想想
You be smart, Calvin.
你有妻子  还有儿子需要抚养
You have a wife and a little boy to raise.
别插手了
Walk away.
别插手
Walk away?
你把我从爸那儿救走
I'm not the dumb little shit I was
第一次带我去兄弟会
when you saved me from Dad,
我再也不像以前那么无知了
took me to my first rally.
我不可能不参与的
There is no walking away from it.
我与兄弟会共存
I am the Brotherhood.
照顾好你的家庭
Take care of your family.
不要跑到我家来让我
Don't you come in here and tell me
照顾好我的家庭  你这个叛徒
to take care of my family, you fucking traitor.
我们会弄死你的
We will fucking bury you.
听到没
You hear me?
要小心哦  哥
Better watch your back, big brother.
今天不太顺吧  凯
Tough day, Kai?
看样子家庭重聚了啊
So, I see there's been a family reunion.
那么  凯  我他妈的到底要跟谁做生意
Now, tell me, Kai, who the fuck am I in business with?
你  还是她
You or her?
是跟我们做生意
You're in business with us.
这么说是没错
So you say.
不过一个人同意  一个人不同意
But one says yes, the other says no.
我现在都断货了
And now I have no product at all.
我们就是来讨论这个事的
We're here to change all of that.
你没带货来啊
You didn't pull up in a truck.
收下这个礼物和我们的提议
Accept this gift and our proposal,
明天我们免费给你一车货
there'll be a truck tomorrow free of charge.
明朝的剑果然好
Ming made a great fucking sword.
不过锋不锋利  还是要带到战场上
But you can never tell the real quality of a blade
试试看才知道
until it's used in battle.
你的提议是什么
What's the proposal?
慢点  慢点  别噎着
Slowly, slowly, slowly. Take your time.
别着急  慢慢吃  慢慢吃
It's okay. Take your time. Take your time.
你心里一直憋着一股怒气
You've been angry for such a long time.
能让你不去害怕
That anger is there to protect you from fear.
可以说那种害怕
Now, we could argue that the fear
来自一个暴力酗酒的父亲
comes from an abusive and drunk father,
但它从哪产生其实不重要
but it doesn't really matter where it comes from.
重要的是  它能被打败
What matters is that it can be beaten.
我会让你摆脱这个包袱
I'm gonna rid you of that burden
帮你达到你的潜力
so you can reach your potential.
那时你就准备好了
And then you're gonna be ready.
准备好做什么
Ready for what?
再当兵吗
The army again?
不
No.
不是当兵
Not the army.
别的事
Something different.
嘿  邦克
Hey, Bunk.
奥特
Otto.
贾斯帕和布莱斯向你问好
Jasper and Bryce send their best.
谢了
Thanks.
你是要像个娘炮一样站那儿
So you gonna stand there all day like a pussy?
-还是打算过来玩玩  -嘿  走开
- Or you gonna come over here and play? - Hey, clear out.
立刻
Now.
我不会说第二次
I'm not gonna tell you again.
走吧
Let's go.
-咱们还会再见  邦克  -放开他
- We'll be seeing you, Bunk. - Get off him!
我知道你还会见我
I know you're gonna be seeing me
因为老子要去找你
'cause I'm gonna be coming for you.
咱们都知道你没有支援就是个娘炮
And we both know what a fucking pussy you are without your backup.
-放开他  -操
- Get off him! - Fucker!
-邦克  放开他  -我靠
- Bunker, let him go. - Come on!
妈的  没用
Shit. It's not working.
听着  继续试试
Now look, keep going.
-别放弃  -但请闭嘴
- Don't give up. - But please do shut up.
你他妈搞的我没法集中注意力
You're breaking my motherfucking concentration.
走
Go!
墨菲  离开这里
Murphy! Get out there!
你去把那女的带到我这里
You get the girl, bring her to me.
快去
Go!
闭嘴
Shut up!
咱们得快点了  老头
We got to hurry the fuck up, old man.
听着  打断大拇指
Look, just break the thumb.
糖果  你确定
Sugar, are you sure?
这是唯一的办法能让他
That's the only way he can get--
这真是把好剑
This is a good fucking sword!
我们得送你上车
We need to get you in the car.
没人能把我从我的地盘赶出去
No one's chasing me out of my place of business.
-我们被困在里面了  -那我们就杀出去
- We'll be trapped inside. - Then we'll fight our way out.
老大  我恳请您再考虑
Sir, I respectfully urge you to recons--
这是我的办公室
This is my office.
所有人出去  快点  动起来
Everybody out. Come on. Move!
你听到了吗
You hear that, man?
从这里传出来的
Coming from over here.
快点
Come on, man.
好了  贱人  咱们走
Okay, bitch. Let's go.
你好啊
Well, hello there.
-他们去哪儿了  -我不知道
- Where the hell are they? - Pssh, I don't know.
咋了  赶紧离开这儿
What? Let's get the fuck out of here.
快啊
Come on.
小心
Hold it!
我去
God!
我绕着走吸引火力
I'm gonna circle around and draw his fire.
-准备  -走
- Ready? - Go!
-糖果  -安全
- Sugar! - I'm clear.
手榴弹
Grenade!
嘿  宝贝
Hey, baby.
还记得我吗
Remember me?
谁能忘了这么一张丑脸
Who could forget a face that fucking ugly?
不赖啊
Not bad.
你一直藏在我眼皮底下
You've been holding out on me.
你打架比做爱在行
You fight better than you fuck.
瞄准你了  混蛋
I got you, you motherfucker.
太他妈恶心了
Oh, fucking messy.
你不喜欢我杀人的方式
You don't like the way I kill,
那下一个你来杀
you kill the next one.
搞定
Done.
没人喜欢爱装逼的人
No one likes a wiseass.
操
Fuck.
雷诺克斯
Lennox!
Lennox.
我
I--
你好  弗拉奇尔
Hello, Frazier.
-普罗科特  -没错
- Proctor. - That's right.
我说过你惹错了人
I told you you were making a mistake.
你想到新交易了吗
Is there a new deal you have in mind?
对  但不是和你
Yeah, but not with you.
我知道你现在看不到周围景象
Now, I know you can't see the room right now,
所以我尽力帮你描述一下
so I'll do my best to describe it for you.
地板上有三个人
You got three men on the floor.
全死了
They're all dead.
你兄弟雷诺克斯  躺在你脚边
Your buddy Lennox, he's at your feet
血流不止  垂死挣扎
slowly bleeding to death.
表情十分痛苦
He appears distraught.
我跟我侄女丽贝卡以及博登在这里
I'm here with my niece Rebecca and Burton.
你认识博登的
You know Burton.
还有我们的好伙伴赫克托·莫拉莱斯
And our mutual associate Hector Morales.
赫克托刚拿到一把新剑
Now, Hector, he has a beautiful new sword.
是我专门送他的礼物
It was a gift I got him for this very occasion.
你也闻到了
And, as you can smell,
我在抽你最高级的雪茄
I'm smoking one of your most excellent cigars.
你跟魔鬼做了交易
You made a deal with the devil,
傻逼德国佬
you stupid Dutchie.
别这么叫我  我不喜欢
Don't call me that. I don't like that.
你会付出代价的  凯
You're gonna pay for this, Kai.
谁都一样
We all pay eventually.
不过我付出代价的时候  你没机会看到了
But in my case, you won't be around to see it.
是没机会听到
Or rather hear about it.
你好
Hey there.
你个蠢货
You stupid cerote.
你难道不知道他会像玩我一样玩你吗
Don't you know he's gonna fuck you like he fucked me?
不  是你玩死了自己  瞎子
No, you fucked yourself, blind man.
其实  我一直没机会
You know, I never did get to thank you
当面谢谢你
in person for the...
给我的那份小礼物
little gift you gave me.
每次摸那道疤都会想到你
I think of you every time I feel it.
动手吧
Just do it.
真够尴尬的
Oh, that's just embarrassing.
我从不失手
I never miss.
抱歉花了这么长时间
Sorry I took so long.
我从来没怀疑过你
I never doubted you for a minute.
你不是说他会为了救我们而死吗
I thought you said he'd get killed trying to save us.
但我一直相信他会来
Yeah, but I never doubted he'd come.
凯莉在那里
Where's Carrie?
胡德
Hood!
放下枪  不然我就崩了她
Put the gun down or I'll blow her head off.
-不要  -快点  我说到做到
- No. - Do it. I will kill her.
-你马上放她走  -没跟你开玩笑
- You let her go now. - I'm not fucking with you!
-放开她  -你他妈给我把枪放下  胡德
- Let her go. - Put the fucking gun down, Hood!
-你马上放开她  -别玩我  我会杀了她
- Let her go now. - Don't play me! I will kill her!
-你不会的  -你他妈把枪放下
- No, you're not. - Put the fucking gun down!
戈登
Gordon!
糖果  帮帮我
Sugar, help me get this.
把背心脱了  快点
Come on, get the vest off. Come on.
操  压着点
Fuck! Put pressure on it.
我来  我能行
I got it. I got it.
我就在这里  戈登  会没事的
I'm right here, Gordon. Everything's gonna be just fine here.
你不会有事
You're gonna be fine.
我操
Fuck me.
发动吧  我这就过去
Start it up. I'm on my way.
-坚持住  -我撑不过去了
- Hold on. - I'm not gonna make it.
别这样说  你会没事的
Don't talk like that. You're gonna be fine.
-我们能把你救出去  -宝贝  我撑不住了
- We're gonna get you out of here. - Baby, I'm not gonna make it.
家里不是只有你一个人会用枪
You're not the only gunslinger in the family.
你为什么要这么做
Why did you do this?
我是来带你回家的  卡莉
I came to take you home, Carrie.
我对你的爱从没停过
I never stopped loving you.
你知道的  对吧
You know that, right?
我爱你  撑住
I love you. Stay with me.
贾伯
Job.
没事的
It's okay.
你要好好的
You be good, okay?
凯迪店
你准备告诉我今天到底怎么回事吗
You want to tell me what the hell happened out there today?
我回来了  很多人很不满
A lot of those guys are angry that I'm back.
他们觉得被背叛了
They feel betrayed.
我知道
Yeah. Yeah, I got that.
不  我说的是你抓了一个平民
No, I meant the part where you grabbed a civilian
在整个餐厅的人面前想掐死他
and started strangling him in front of a diner full of witnesses.
-对不起  -对不起  去他妈的对不起
- Sorry about that. - You're sorry? Fuck sorry, okay?
我也不喜欢那种人
I don't like those guys any more than you do,
-但你要是不喜欢警徽  -我就是那种人
- but if you're gonna wear that badge-- - I am guys like that!
他有过的那种肮脏龌龊的想法
Every evil, twisted thought that he has had,
我也有过
I have had.
他做的每件操蛋事
Every fucked-up thing that he's done,
我都做过
I have done.
我做过好多恶心的事
I've done things that would make you sick.
他们让我恶心
They make me sick.
你觉得这地方只有你一个人有污点吗
You think you're the only one around here that's got dirt on him?
我也做过  一些事
I've done some... things.
邦克  我
Look, Bunker, I--
我不了解你
I don't know you, okay?
但在我看来
But from what I've seen,
你已经不是原来那样了
you're not the man you used to be.
我会一直是那样
I will always be that man.
穿上这身制服也无法洗净我的罪孽
Putting on this uniform does not wipe my slate clean.
我在尽我所能地做出些改变
I'm doing everything I can to change.
每过一段时间
And every once in a while...
我都要告诉自己
I manage to convince myself
我已经变得更好了
that I'm a better person.
但我一接触到
But the minute that I come into contact
那帮混蛋
with one of those fucking guys
看到他们看我的那种眼神
and see the way that they look at me,
我内心就充满了恨意
all I feel is hate
和愤怒
and anger
我根本摆脱不掉
and I can't shake it.
好的  听我说
Okay, all right. Listen to me.
等等  看着我
Listen, listen. Hold it. Look at me.
你所感受到的并不是愤怒
Okay, that isn't anger that you're feeling.
而是羞耻和负罪感
That's the shame and the guilt.
相信我  我们都有这种感觉
And trust me, we all feel that.
大家都有
All of us.
所以我们才比他们好
And that is what makes you better than them.
如果你感受不到
If you didn't feel that,
我才会开始担心你  知道吗
that's when I'd start to worry, all right?
懂了吗
You hear me?
好的
Okay.
现在  你能向我保证
Now, look, can you promise me
今天发生的事不会再发生了吗
that what happened out there today is never gonna happen again?
我不知道
I don't know.
答得好
Good answer.
因为要是你满口答应  那肯定是胡扯
'Cause if you had said yes, I knew you were full of shit.
回家吧  好好睡一觉
Go home, all right? Get some sleep.
谢谢  长官
Thank you, sir.
没问题
Yep.
迈尔斯餐厅
我刚从州警那逃出来
I just hung up with the state police.
上帝啊  胡德
Jesus Christ, Hood.
戈登·霍普韦尔死了吗
Gordon Hopewell is dead?
那到底发生什么事儿了
What the hell happened out there?
他说热那亚基地像战场一样
He said Camp Genoa looks like a war zone.
是啊  哪天有机会我肯定告诉你
Yeah, I'll have to tell you about it someday.
不  不要哪天
No, no, not someday.
他说刑事调查局一个小时内就能到
He said that CID is gonna be here in less than an hour.
我要你现在就把事情说明白
We need to get your story straight.
他们会找你谈话的  布罗克
They're coming to talk to you, Brock.
你是什么意思
What are you talking about?
胡德
Hood?
警徽和辞职信在我桌上了
Badge and letter of resignation on my desk.
你开玩笑呢吗  胡德
Are you kidding? Hey! Hood!
你去哪儿
Where you going?
你不能
You can't--
就这么走了
you can't just leave.
这次我可不忍你了
Well, I'm not giving it back this time.
我对你很失望  柯特
I'm disappointed in you, Kurt.
但路是你选的
But the choice is yours to make.
如果你还要继续穿那身警皮
If you're gonna wear that cop uniform,
我这儿的皮你就别要了
you can't wear mine.
是谁带走他的
Who in the hell took him?
不知道
I don't know.
我们怎么找他
How do we find him?
不知道
No idea.
通常这时候贾伯就来了
Usually that's where Job comes in.
你还能找谁吗
Isn't there anyone you can reach out--
我操  我真他妈不知道
God damn it, Sugar. I don't fucking know.
我不知道谁抓的他  不知道他在哪
I don't know who took him. I don't know where he is.
我他妈也不知道怎么把他弄回来
And I don't know how to fucking get him back.
操
Fuck.
他能联系到我们之前  只能孤军奋战
Till we hear from him, he's on his own.
你好像是新来的
Hey, you look like a new man.
就是说你在这房间里的时间
Which means your time in this room
没有了
is done.
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫道尔顿
My name is Dalton.
你是当兵的
Are you military?
曾经是
I was.
现在我们招募你这样的人
But now I recruit men like you.
培养他们成为精英队
I develop them for an elite unit.
什么队
What unit?
哪支部队的
What branch?
没错
Exactly.
我的方法非常不传统
My methods are very unorthodox.
我只有很少的时间可以评价你的能力
I have a very small window of time in which to assess your ability.
我什么方面的能力
My ability to do what?
把需要完成的事完成的能力
To do what needs to be done.
我们要是合作  应该挺愉快的
I think we could do some very good work together.
要是我不感兴趣呢
And if I'm not interested?
没事  随你走
That's fine. You're free to go.
但你要是感兴趣  就可以子承父业了
But if you do, you'll always be your father's son.
我跟他一点都不像
I'm nothing like him.
你那帮大胡子朋友呢
What happened to your friends with the beards?
都死了
They're all dead.
你生存能力确实很强
You sure do have a knack for survival.
你见死不救  警长
You left me there to die, Sheriff.
我不是警长
I'm not the sheriff.
你想要什么  道歉吗
What do you want, an apology?
不是
No.
换我也会这么做
I would have done the same thing.
警长这活根本不适合你
You know, being the sheriff never really suited you.
是不适合
No, it didn't.
干我
Fuck me.